sporteluxe.com 2017-08-07

# PRIVACY - Sporteluxe

This following document sets forth the Privacy Policy for the _SPORTELUXE_ website, _www.sporteluxe.com_.

_Sporteluxe_ is committed to providing you with the best possible customer service experience. _Sporteluxe_ is bound by the Privacy Act 1988 (Crh), which sets out a number of principles concerning the privacy of individuals.

### Collection of your personal information

There are many aspects of the site which can be viewed without providing personal information, however, for access to future _Sporteluxe_ customer support features you are required to submit personally identifiable information. This may include but not limited to a unique username and password, or provide sensitive information in the recovery of your lost password.

### Competitions and Special Offers

Sporteluxe collects personal information from you when you participate in competitions and special offers. If this information is also being collected by a third party other than Sporteluxe, we will notify you at the same time. If you do not want any of your personal information shared, you should not participate in the competitions or special offers we conduct.

### Sharing of your personal information

We may occasionally hire other companies to provide services on our behalf, including but not limited to handling customer support enquiries, processing transactions or customer freight shipping. Those companies will be permitted to obtain only the personal information they need to deliver the service. _Sporteluxe_ takes reasonable steps to ensure that these organisations are bound by confidentiality and privacy obligations in relation to the protection of your personal information.

### Third Parties

Some of the services and advertisements on Sporteluxe.com and within our mobile apps, are delivered or served by third-party companies, which may collect information about your use of the Sporteluxe site.

These companies may place or recognise cookies, Web beacons or other technology to track certain non-personal information about our website users. For example, in the course of serving certain advertisements, an advertiser may place or recognise a unique cookie on your browser in order to collect certain information about your use of the Sporteluxe site. In many cases, this information could be used to show you ads on other websites based on your interests.

We do not have access to, nor control over, these third parties’ use of cookies or other tracking technologies or how they may be used.

We use google Doubleclick to serve advertising on our websites and in our apps. Google serves advertisements onto the Sporteluxe site, which use the Google Doubleclick cookie, and in some cases, a unique device identifier, to show you ads based on your visit to Sporteluxe.com and other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the Google Doubleclick cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences).

You have choices about the collection of information by third parties on the Sporteluxe website:

1) If you would like more about your option not to accept advertiser cookies, please [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/consumer/opt_out.asp).

2) If you would like to opt-out of having interest-based ad targeting, [click here](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/).

Your access to our Sporteluxe websites should not be affected if you do not accept cookies served by third parties.

### Use of your personal information

For each visitor to reach the site, we expressively collect the following non-personally identifiable information, including but not limited to browser type, version and language, operating system, pages viewed while browsing the Site, page access times and referring website address. This collected information is used solely internally for the purpose of gauging visitor traffic, trends and delivering personalized content to you while you are at this Site.

From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will use for these new purposes only, data collected from the time of the policy change forward will adhere to our updated practices.

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

_Sporteluxe_ reserves the right to make amendments to this Privacy Policy at any time. If you have objections to the Privacy Policy, you should not access or use the Site.

### Accessing Your Personal Information

You have a right to access your personal information, subject to exceptions allowed by law. If you would like to do so, please let us know. You may be required to put your request in writing for security reasons. _Sporteluxe_ reserves the right to charge a fee for searching for, and providing access to, your information on a per request basis.

### Contacting us

_Sporteluxe_ welcomes your comments regarding this Privacy Policy. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy and would like further information, please contact us by any of the following means during business hours Monday to Friday.

Email: hello@sporteluxe.com _  
_

Post: Attn: Privacy Policy,  
_Sporteluxe,  
4/119 McEvoy Street,  
Waterloo, NSW 2017,  
AUSTRALIA_
